[MUSIC PLAYS ON LAPTOPS]
All right, just a few more feet and...
(Howard:)Here we are, gentlemen,
the Gates of Elzebub.
SHELDON: Good Lord.
RAJESH: Oh.
(Leonard:)Don't panic. This is what the last
97 hours have been about.
Stay frosty. There's a horde of goblins...
(Howard:)...on the other side of that gate
guarding the Sword of Azeroth.
(Leonard:)Warriors, unsheathe your weapons.
Magic wielders, raise your wands.
(Sheldon:)Lock and load.
Raj, blow the gates.
(Raj:)Blowing the gates.
Control-shift-B.
[RUMBLING AND GOBLINS
SCREAMING ON LAPTOPS]
(Raj:)- Oh, my God, so many goblins.
HOWARD: Aah!
(Howard:)Don't just stand there. Slash and move.
(Leonard:)Stay in formation.
- Leonard, you got one on your tail.
- That's all right, my tail's prehensile.
I got him, Leonard.
(Raj:)Tonight, I spice my meat
with goblin blood.
Raj, it's a trap. They're flanking us.